IObit Driver Booster 12 Update History

V12.6 2025.07.25
+ Supported updating drivers for more new devices, including GeForce RTX 5050
+ More Game Ready drivers to improve gaming performance, such as Mecha BREAK, Diablo IV, Monster Hunter Wilds, Cyberpunk 2077, Valorant, and Grand Theft Auto V Enhanced
+ Minor language improvements
+ Fixed known issues

V12.5 2025.06.03
+ Supported updating drivers for more new devices, such as Nvidia GeForce RTX 5060, and AMD Radeon RX 9070 GRE
+ Supported updating more game drivers to improve game performance, including DOOM: The Dark Ages, Dune: Awakening, EVERSPACE 2, F1 25, Fort Solis, Ghost of Tsushima DIRECTOR'S CUT, InFlux Redux, NARAKA: BLADEPOINT, THE FINALS, and Warhammer 40,000: Darktide
+ Fixed minor bugs

V12.4 2025.04.08
+ Supported updating for more new devices, such as AMD Radeon RX 9000 Series, AMD Ryzen 9 Series CPU, and AMD Ryzen AI CPU
+ Supported updating more game drivers to improve game performance, including The First Berserker: Khazan, KARMA: The Dark World, Rise of the Ronin, Half-Life 2 RTX Demo, inZOI, Warhammer 40,000: Darktide, Assassin's Creed Shadows, The Last of Us Part II Remastered, and Control
+ Optimized Game Boost for a better gaming experience
+ Fixed known bugs

V12.3 2025.02.27
+ Supported updating more drivers for more devices, such as NVIDIA Geforce RTX 5070 Ti, and MTT S80/S70
+ Supported updating more game drivers to improve game performance, such as Sid Meier's Civilization VII, Avowed, Monster Hunter Wilds, and Like a Dragon: Pirate Yakuza in Hawaii
+ Optimized driver update process for better performance
+ Optimized Fix Incompatible Drivers to support ignoring incompatible drivers
+ Fixed known issues

V12.2 2025.01.08
+ Supported updating more game drivers to improve the gaming performance in more games, such as Marvel Rivals, Microsoft Flight Simulator 2024, Dragon Age: The Veilguard, Slitterhead, Delta Force, S.T.A.L.K.E.R. 2: Heart of Chornobyl, Indiana Jones and the Great Circle, Forza Horizon 5, and God of War: Ragnarok
+ Improved the efficiency and fluency of local AI by updating drivers for a better intelligent experience
+ Optimized program logic for a better experience
+ Small optimizations in UI
+ Fixed known issues

V12.1 2024.11.11
+ Newly supported the latest Windows 11 24H2
+ Expanded database to support updating more drivers for more devices
+ Added more game drivers for a better game experience, like Dragon Age: The Veilguard, Alan Wake 2: The Lake House, Unknown 9: Awakening, and Call of Duty: Black Ops 6
+ Added a new tool Fix Incompatible Drivers to check and fix incompatible driver issues (Windows 10 and above)
+ Fixed known issues

V12.0 2024.09.12
+ Expanded database to support updating 15,000,000+ drivers for more devices
+ Supported more new hardware, including Intel Core Ultra, AMD Ryzen 9000 Series, and AMD Ryzen AI 300 Series
+ Latest drivers offered to boost gaming performance and system stability
+ Optimized the scan engine to accelerate scanning by up to 18%
+ Optimized the driver installation engine to increase installation speed by 7% and installation success rate by 25%
+ Improved Game Boost to boost gaming performance by up to 5%
+ Revamped the update program for faster update
+ New modern UI to make it more beautiful and easy-to-use
+ Supported 38 localized languages
+ More can be discovered by you

