<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameSaveManager_Translation>
	<Title>Custom Gamesave Entries</Title>
	<Info>From this page, you can add new detection rules for GameSave Manager to follow.
Modify an officially supported entry to meet your own needs, add an entirely new entry or just manage existing Custom Gamesave Entries right here.</Info>
	<List>
		<Header>Existing entries</Header>
		<NoEntries>No 'Custom Gamesave Entries' currently defined.

To begin, click the 'Add' button below.</NoEntries>
	</List>
	<Wizard>
		<Title>Custom Gamesave Entries Wizard; Step %CURRENT% of %TOTAL%</Title>
		<Header>Custom Gamesave Entries Wizard</Header>
		<Step1>
			<Info>This wizard will guide you through the process of adding--or modifying--a 'Custom Gamesave Entry'.

Throughout this wizard, you'll be asked for various information about the data to backup so please be prepared to answer a few questions.
This process shouldn't take longer than 5 minutes. Remember, you can cancel at any time.

To begin, let's name our Custom Gamesave Entry.
You can call this entry anything you wish, but it's recommended that you call it something meaningful (such as the game's full title).</Info>
			<Name>Entry Title:</Name>
			<Warning>NOTE: If you are defining extra files, paths or registry data to an existing 'Officially Supported Entry', please use the name of said entry to overwrite it with your own definitions.

Your Custom Gamesave Entry will then be populated with the 'Officially Supported' entry's data for you to edit.</Warning>
			<Errors>
				<InvalidName title="Invalid name:" width="420" height="110">The name specified ('%NAME%') is already in use for another Custom Gamesave Entry.

Please specify a different name and try again.</InvalidName>
				<NoName title="No name specified:" width="420" height="110">You've neglected to name your Custom Gamesave Entry.

Please specify a name and try again.</NoName>
			</Errors>
		</Step1>
		<Step2>
			<Info>The form below allows you to specify any warning messages for this entry.
An exclamation icon is used to notify the user of a warning message, and can be viewed via the 'Entry Details' panel upon selection.

If you do not wish to specify any warnings, simply leave the form below blank and click 'Next &gt;'</Info>
			<Backup>Backup warning</Backup>
			<Restore>Restore warning</Restore>
		</Step2>
		<Step3>
			<Info>Using the form below, please specify all files, directories and registry data you wish to backup for this entry.
You may add as many items as you wish.</Info>
			<DirTitle>Files & directories to backup:</DirTitle>
			<RegTitle>Registry data to backup:</RegTitle>
			<Errors>
				<NothingSpecified title="Error:" width="420" height="110">You've neglected to specify anything for this entry to backup.

Please specify at least 1 directory or 1 registry entry and try again.</NothingSpecified>
			</Errors>
		</Step3>
		<Step4>
			<Info>We're finished!
All the required information has been collected and we're ready to save it to the database.

If you wish to change anything, you may do so now or at a later date by editing this entry.</Info>
			<SubmitPanel>
				<Header>Share Entry</Header>
				<Info>This entry appears to meet the criteria to be sent to the GameSave Manager servers for approval.
If approved, this entry will be implemented in a future 'Database Update' and thus benefit the community as a whole.</Info>
				<InfoScene>Despite your entry meeting the criteria for submission, it also appears to contain one or more 'Scene Release' specific save locations.
Such locations are not supported, thus you cannot submit this entry for approval.

If you feel this is a mistake, you may manually submit your entry on our Forums.
Regardless, your Custom Gamesave Entry is completely unaffected.</InfoScene>
				<Submit>Yes, I'd like to share this entry</Submit>
			</SubmitPanel>
		</Step4>
		<DirWizard>
			<Title>Custom Gamesave Entries: Directory Wizard; Step %CURRENT% of %TOTAL%</Title>
			<Header>Custom Gamesave Entries: Directory Wizard</Header>
			<Step1>
				<Info>This wizard will guide you through the process of adding--or modifying-- a directory rule for your Custom Gamesave Entry.

This process shouldn't take longer than a minute.

To begin, would you like GameSave Manager to dynamically detect part of this directory for you?</Info>
				<UseSpecialPaths>Yes please, dynamically detect the following directory</UseSpecialPaths>
				<SpecialPaths>
					<DOCUMENTS>My Documents</DOCUMENTS>
					<SHARED_DOCUMENTS>Shared Documents</SHARED_DOCUMENTS>
					<APPDATA>Application Data</APPDATA>
					<APPDATA_COMMON>Application Data - Common</APPDATA_COMMON>
					<APPDATA_LOCAL>Application Data - Local</APPDATA_LOCAL>
					<APPDATA_LOCALLOW>Application Data - LocalLow</APPDATA_LOCALLOW>
					<PROG_FILES_86>Program Files x86</PROG_FILES_86>
					<STEAM>Steam Installation Directory</STEAM>
					<STEAM_CACHE>Steam Cache</STEAM_CACHE>
					<STEAM_CLOUD>Steam Cloud</STEAM_CLOUD>
					<UPLAY>Ubisoft uPlay cache</UPLAY>
					<FLASH>Macromedia Flash cache</FLASH>
					<SAVED_GAMES>Saved Games</SAVED_GAMES>
					<USER_PROFILE>User Home</USER_PROFILE>
					<REGISTRY>From Registry Value</REGISTRY>
				</SpecialPaths>
			</Step1>
			<Reg>
				<Info>Please use the form below to specify the 'registry value' which contains the directory you wish to dynamically detect.

NOTE: Filenames are automatically stripped from the value (for example, "C:\Game\Launch.exe" becomes "C:\Game").</Info>
				<Hive>Registry Hive:</Hive>
				<Path>Registry Path:</Path>
				<Value>Registry Value:</Value>
				<Test>Test Detection</Test>
			</Reg>
			<Step2>
				<InfoWithSpecialPath>We now need to append the remainder of the path to the end of the directory we've previously specified to dynamically detect.

To do this, simply enter the remainder of the directory path in the field below.
If you do not need to append anything to the dynamically detected path, leave the field blank and click 'Next &gt;'.</InfoWithSpecialPath>
				<InfoWithoutSpecialPath>As you've chosen not to dynamically detect a directory, you now need to specify the full path below.

If you wish to go back and enable Dynamic Detection, feel free to click "&lt; Back".</InfoWithoutSpecialPath>
				<DynamicDetection>Dynamic Detection</DynamicDetection>
				<Append>Append the following</Append>
				<Full>Look in the following directory</Full>
			</Step2>
			<Step3>
				<Info>Finally, we need to specify what files to backup.

You can use 'wildcards' (* and ?) within filenames you specify.

Examples:
	*.* - Processes all files
	*.sav - Processes all '.sav' file types
	My*.sav - Processes all '.sav' file types that begin with 'my'
	MySave.sav - Processes the file 'MySave.sav' within the root directory
	bin\MySave.sav - Processes the file 'MySave.sav' within the 'bin' sub-folder
	bin\*.* - Processes all files within the 'bin' sub-folder</Info>
				<Warning>NOTE: Separate files with a pipex (for example *.sav|*.ini)</Warning>
				<IncludedFiles>Files to include</IncludedFiles>
				<ExcludedFiles>Files to exclude</ExcludedFiles>
			</Step3>
		</DirWizard>
		<RegWizard>
			<Title>Custom Gamesave Entries: Registry Wizard</Title>
			<Header>Custom Gamesave Entries: Registry Wizard</Header>
			<Info>Please enter the Registry Key details below to backup.</Info>
			<Hive>Registry Hive:</Hive>
			<Path>Registry Path:</Path>
			<DefinedValues>
				<Header>Registry Values:</Header>
				<EntireKey>Backup entire key</EntireKey>
				<Specific>Backup the following value(s):</Specific>
				<Values>Values:</Values>
				<Info>Separate value names with a pipex ( | ).</Info>
			</DefinedValues>
		</RegWizard>
	</Wizard>
	<SubmissionMessage>
		<Header>Submission Message</Header>
		<Info>You're about to submit your Custom Gamesave Entry titled '%NAME%' to the GameSave Manager server for approval.

Would you like to specify a submission message?</Info>
		<NoMsg>No thanks, just submit my entry</NoMsg>
		<Msg>Yes please, I'd like to specify some additional information</Msg>
		<ReturnCodes>
			<NoConnection title="Error" width="420" height="110">There was an error when trying to communicate with the GameSave Manager server.
Perhaps it's offline or you don't have an active internet connection?</NoConnection>
			<DBUpdate title="Error" width="420" height="110">There appears to be a Database Update for you.

Please apply the update and try again.</DBUpdate>
			<DynError title="Error" width="420" height="110">The entry was unable to be submitted due to an issue with it's 'Dynamic Detection'</DynError>
			<DupError title="Error" width="420" height="110">This entry already appears to of been submitted by yourself or someone else.</DupError>
			<Banned title="Error" width="420" height="110">We've recieved too many spam submissions from your IP address.
Please try submitting manually via our Forums</Banned>
			<MissingData title="Error" width="420" height="110">Entry appears to be missing some required data.</MissingData>
			<Update title="Error" width="420" height="110">This version of GameSave Manager is no longer supported by the server.
Please update to the latest version and try again.</Update>
			<Maintenance title="Error" width="420" height="110">The submission system appears to be down for maintenance.
Please try again later, or submit the entry manually via our Forums</Maintenance>
			<SubmitError title="Error" width="420" height="110">There was an unknown error when submitting the entry.
Please try again later, or submit the entry manually via our Forums</SubmitError>
			<Success title="Success" width="420" height="110">Your entry titled '%NAME%' has successfully been submitted and is now awaiting approval.
			
			Thank you.</Success>
		</ReturnCodes>
	</SubmissionMessage>
	<Errors>
		<InvalidEntry title="Error:" width="420" height="110">The 'Custom Gamesave Entry' selected doesn't appear to be valid, or an error occured while querying the database for required data.

Please try again.</InvalidEntry>
	</Errors>
</GameSaveManager_Translation>